Oh, hey, Sina.
Damn meat.
She has some nerve ignoring me like that.
I'm pretty sure I'm the one she was ignoring.
Oh, yes! Conquer me on Friday night!
I want more in my hands than just my scepter!
Hey, just what the hell do you think you're doing, Yosara?
Get your claws off!
What is this?
You heard what I said. Hands up, you harpy!
Subjugate me!
Grant me your legendary rigid blade, I beg you!
Oh, good sir, you are truly a knight to remember!
What the hell are you doing?
I should be the one asking you that, Jugzy.
What kind of pervert watches smut in a church?
It is not smut, you idiot.
It's Black Star the Sacred Sword,
and it's one of the hottest video games
in the market right now.
An epic romance fantasy adventure for the ages.
It's loaded with action and romance.
The brave knight Lucas has to defeat Varnabal,
the god of destruction.
In the scene you so rudely interrupted,
Princess Cecilia was proclaimed
her true love for Lucas.
She was opening her castle gates to him.
Didn't you know it was one of those adults-only games?
No, how was I supposed to?
After Sparkling School Life 7,
I wanted a new game,
so I checked out some online forums.
They all said this was the hottest game right now.
And then when I asked this guy in class about it,
he gave me a copy and said it would be perfect for me.
It sure was, pervert!
Are you jealous or just drinking Haterade?
As if, you freak! Perfbag!
Sicko! Kinkmeister!
Porn addict! Double D Deviant!
Pneumatic knocker nympho!
Get away before I catch pornitis from you!
Why do I have to put up with abuse like this
just for playing a video game?
Okay, fine.
I'll admit the game does have a couple of steamy scenes in it.
But that isn't anything out of the ordinary.
Go to the library once in a while,
and you'll see the same things you're giving me crap for
in the classics.
So slow your roll.
This game's a work of art,
just like they are.
I've never seen your eyes glued to art
the way they were to that game.
Just be honest
and admit you're addicted to the pervy stuff.
No, I'm not.
I just wanted to help Lucas and Cecilia
consummate their relationship,
to help them do what happens
when a man and woman fall in love with each other.
What you're seeing here is love, not sex.
Get your nasty porn away!
It's romantic.
There's nothing nasty about it at all.
You could have fooled me.
I'm sorry that you're such a freaking prude
you can't appreciate it.
you can't appreciate the artistic merits of this scene.
Well, if it is art,
then please read what they're saying out loud, Jiggles.
If it truly is an inoffensive work of art,
then you should have no problem doing what I asked.
Right?
Of course not!
It's just that I get a little nervous
reading out loud in front of people.
In that case, I'll do it too.
Hm?
Say what?
I'll also read from an artistic work.
The boobs has to go first.
It's just art, right?
She shouldn't have a problem
if that game isn't smut
and the heroine isn't some promiscuous princess
hoping to get a hold of Lucas's mighty sword
or his fabled family jewels.
Hey, don't turn their pure love
into something that's dirty.
Okay, if you want me to read it out loud,
then I'll do it.
Um, my dear Lucas,
please cleave my, um, heaving...
bosom with your rigid blade.
Louder, I can't hear you.
And let me hold the sword that makes maidens coo.
I want to see it in the masterful strokes
that you so deftly employ in its use.
Show me your big weapon.
Oh, so you want me to unsheathe my sacred sword, do you?
My, what a randy and demanding tart
you've revealed yourself to be, Cecilia.
No, you speak coarse things that are not true.
Nonsense, I can see that lusting expression in your eyes.
Look, if you want something, don't deny it, ask for it.
Or to be more specific, beg for it, tart.
Please, I beg of thee, my carnal cavalier.
This randy-minded royal wants, nay, needs...
Your sacred sword.
Don't say sacred sword.
Say the name of what you really want.
Don't stop now.
Go on and finish it off.
Lucas, please. I want it. All of it.
You're...
Robbing...
Gigantic...
Mighty...
Ravishing...
I can't say that!
You suck, Yelthera! You're the worst!
That was a bit overboard, even for you.
I hope the audio came out okay.
I was recording Meat the whole time she was reading.
I think I'll play her little smut recital over the PA system.
Are you the devil?!
Now my turn.
For what?
I said I would do it, and I'm keeping my word.
So I'm going to read from a work of art like I promised.
Why does my heart feel so ashamed?
Autumn mountain shadow on a day of white wind?
Uncannily mature tree trunks stood,
in hollows thick with the fallen leaves.
Wow, that's pretty deep.
Hey, sis, I'm home.
There.
K-K-K.
Ah, my mortal servant has finally returned.
Your vampiric master is quite famished, so I do hope you've brought me a sacrifice.
I'll get dinner started, Cobito.
Hmm.
That name is only my human alias.
My proper name is...
Racist V Felicity Sumeragi.
Child of darkness and true heir to the great night tribe.
I must quench my thirst and feed worm.
K-K-K.
Bring forth my sustenance now, or grave disaster will befall you.
Whatever night spawn.
You'll never see the light.
K-K-K.
Dinner's ready, sis.
Your sacrifice.
Well done, slave.
A human's lifeblood is incredibly delicious.
It's tomato juice, dork.
And now, here's a tale of two furry felons.
Remember Chim-Chim, the young monkey at the Takayama Zoo who...
Hey, eat your onions too, Cobito.
Here.
Attagirl.
By the way, my human brother, I've noticed that you've been late providing my sacrifices recently.
Oh, right.
I haven't been getting home as early as usual because of the club.
You better get used to it.
What's more important to you, me or that club of yours?
The club, of course.
If you want dinner early, make it yourself.
We're out of tomato juice.
I mean we're out of the precious lifeblood of humans.
I'll get some tomorrow.
Thanks, Kodaka.
I mean, you better get it, you human wretch.
About a year ago, my kid sister Kobito got addicted to this anime series called Full Metal Necromancer.
Since then, she's been acting and talking like she's this character on the show who's a vampire.
I spent my first couple of years in this house when I was a little kid.
We left it ten years ago when my dad had to move because of work and it's been sitting empty ever since.
When dad found out he was getting transferred to America recently, he decided Kobito and I would stay in Japan.
So her vampiric majesty and I moved back here.
But it's been so long I barely remember anything about this place at all.
Kobito, your bath's ready.
After this show, mortal.
I guess the club really is important to me.
Hmm?
Hey, why aren't you playing porn star today?
That's black star, you idiot!
I didn't want any more crap, so I brought Sparkling School Life 7, but it appears the harpy isn't here.
She said some book she wants goes on sale today.
Hey, tell me something.
Um, can you swim?
Yeah, kinda, sorta.
Really?
Well, in that case, do you think maybe you can teach me how to do it?
You mean, you don't know how to?
No, because none of the schools I've attended ever offered swimming lessons.
Uh, okay, sure.
I don't mind teaching you, but why do you want to learn all of a sudden?
Jeez, you really are a dumb blonde, aren't you?
Now that I'm friends with Natsumi, how awkward is it gonna be if we go to a pool or a beach and I don't know how to swim?
But she's not real.
You can teach me at Sea God's Palace Land this Sunday.
Sure.
All right, then.
Let's get one thing straight.
Don't you dare tell Yozara I don't know how to swim.
You understand me?
Isn't Udder's coming to the club today?
No, she said she had some shopping to do.
For what?
Some kind of milking device?
Don't you dare tell Yozara I don't know how to swim.
Hey, is something on your mind?
No.
Is that the new book you were talking about?
It sure is.
Any good?
So far.
You're ten minutes late.
Uh, sorry.
Sorry.
Sorry for the wait.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just need a cold shower.
Here.
I don't need help getting in.
Okay, first you're going to try to open your eyes underwater.
Hey, give me some credit.
I can't swim, but I can at least do that.
See?
I gotcha.
Then let's move on to the harder stuff, okay?
Man, she sure learns quick.
Here you go.
Thanks a lot.
Thanks so much for giving me swimming lessons today.
If Natsumi and I ever go swimming, now I'll know what to do.
Yeah, like that'll happen in the real world.
This place sure is swanky for a water park, isn't it?
Yeah, but it's on the verge of bankruptcy.
Are you serious?
Look around.
There's hardly anybody here.
The last time the mayor came over, he and Daddy were wondering how much longer this place
could last.
Daddy?
Oh, you mean the president of St. Chronicus?
Yep.
Speaking of your dad, I haven't had a chance to meet the guy.
I need to stop by sometime and pay my respects.
Wait!
Why on earth would you want to pay your respects to my father?
Do you mean to tell me that you think that today is an actual date you and I are on?
And you want to meet my daddy to get his permission to officially start dating me?
I'm sorry to burst your bubble.
Huh?
But I want to meet him because he did me a favor since he and my dad are old friends.
I'd like to drop by to thank him for helping me with the admission process to get into the
academy.
Well, you should have said so in the first place, you jackass.
Hey, you're the one whose imagination ran wild.
Come on, admit it.
What you said was really suggestive.
Geez, meat.
Excuse me?
Um, well, what I meant to say was, geez, the meat in these fried noodles is so tender.
I don't think that is what you meant.
You're just a little hypersensitive whenever the word meat is mentioned.
Can you blame me?
I have been since Hozera started calling me that.
If it bugs you so much, then why do you answer whenever anybody says the word?
Because it's the first time anyone gave me a nickname.
Oh?
So getting one actually made me a little happy.
Whoa, for real?
Yes, but don't ever tell Yozera I said that.
Now, if you're finally done stuffing your face, let's get back to my swimming lessons.
Just give me a minute.
If I was her, I'd be pissed if someone called me meat.
But a nickname does make you feel special.
Taka.
Hey, Taka.
With you?
No way.
Stuck up bitch?
Yeah, right?
I won't go out with you, so I'm a bitch, huh?
Well, I'd much rather be a bitch than date the three of you losers.
You slut.
Oh, crap.
Here we go.
Oh, so I'm a bitch and a slut?
If that's how you closet cases talk to all the girls who turn you down, then maybe you
dorks should just date each other.
Watch your mouth, slut face.
Hey, check it out, bros.
This chick's shaking like a leaf.
Yeah, totally.
Aw, you're scared of us, ain't ya?
No, I'm not shaking because I'm afraid.
I'm shaking because I'm angry, jerk.
Senna.
Oh, Taka.
What do you want, brah?
The girl you're messing with is with me.
Oh, we had no idea, dude.
She never mentioned a boyfriend.
Tase.
Hey, wait a minute.
You creeps aren't getting away with calling me bitch, slut, and tease.
So get down on your knees and beg and grovel for my forgiveness now.
You heard me, piss-ants.
Do it.
Like hell we will.
Violence is never the answer.
Let go of my hand.
Yeah, douche.
Yes.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Take my advice and just walk away from this, guys, okay?
Uh, sure thing.
Good choice, boys.
I'm glad we could agree.
You okay?
That dude was psycho.
Nice work, badass.
You can lick my feet as a reward if you'd like to.
You sure showed those guys.
Sheesh, what a bunch of morons, right?
There was only one moron here, and that was you.
Me?
How do you mean?
Why did you have to keep pushing it with those guys?
They were leaving, but you just couldn't shut the hell up.
What?
Like they didn't have it coming?
Why are you giving me a lecture anyway?
Rude much?
Because you need a lecture right now.
There are a lot of guys out there who were even nastier than they were.
You could have gotten hurt just then.
I'm not always going to be around to protect you, you know.
Yeah, well, who cares?
I'll protect myself.
You don't have to worry about me, dude.
The way you're acting, I sure as hell do.
Wow.
You really are worried about me.
All right, then.
I apologize, okay?
From now on, I promise I'll be more careful.
Great.
Thanks.
I think I'm done for today.
That's the first time a boy my age has ever admitted he was worried about me.
Well, I'll see ya.
Right.
Um, as for today, thanks for everything.
We should go again soon.
I'd like to try out that wave pool next time.
Uh, yeah, sure.
I wonder what put her in such a good mood.
Time to take you down, punk.
Teach the weakling a lesson.
Talk about deja vu.
This reminds me of some of the fights I got in as a kid.
I'm sorry.
Mortal brother, help me!
Colbito, what's the matter, huh?
It's the bath.
I almost perished in that infernal thing.
What?
How?
The water turned cold.
This wouldn't have happened if it had been filled with the more blood.
Would you put something on, at least?
Oh, the horror!
Why don't you pick on someone who's not so weak?
Why don't you make me?
Hey, what was that for?
I was trying to help you, butthole.
You're wrong.
I'll prove I'm not weak.
Then bring it on, blondie.
Don't ignore me!
Jerk!
Get him, guys!
After the fight broke up, me and that kid actually became friends.
Taka.
Huh?
Do you know what my mom told me one time?
She said that in first grade, it's okay if you can't make 100 friends.
What matters is if you can make real friends, and ones who mean more to you than 100 different
others would.
Even if you only make one real friend, that's better than having 100 who are just okay.
I feel the same way your mom does.
So how about we agree to be each other's one real friend for the rest of our lives?
Even if you never make any others, I promise I'll be your real friend forever.
Hey, why are you getting so mushy all of a sudden?
You're the one who started all that real friend stuff.
Sorry.
Guess I sounded kind of girly, huh?
I must have dozed off.
What matters is if you can make real friends, and ones who mean more to you than 100 different
others would.
Right.
What?
Kodaka.
You remember?
Wait, what did you say?
Oh, it was nothing.
You were asleep and just started muttering.
It surprised me.
Sorry about that.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Hey, where'd Sina go?
Me'd already went home.
And you're still here?
Yes.
I was reading my book and lost track of time.
Oh, well, I've got to get going.
That kid.
I wonder whatever happened to him.
Does he still live here?
And his nickname.
What did I call him again?
For the life of me, I can't seem to remember.
Maybe he's in the same boat.
After 10 years, I'm sure he doesn't remember me or what I said either.
I was just a kid when I said it, but is there even such a thing?
Real friends who last forever?
I don't know.
Hey, Yozara, tell me, do you know how to swim?
That's a stupid question, Fun Bags,
because I can do everything.
That sucks big time.
If you said no, I was going to offer to teach you how.
Well, as long as you got down on your knees
and begged me, of course.
Ever since someone gave me private swimming lessons recently,
I've really wanted to pass on what I had learned.
Wait, someone gave you lessons?
Who taught you and your pontoons how to swim?
Noah, never mind what I said.
Next, underclassmen don't hold back.
Underclassmen?
Is the club getting a new member or something?
How should I know, Boobsie?
I'll see you next time.